{
  "currentCase": {
    "id": 1234567890,
    "statusName": "Relief",
    "dateOfApproach": "2022-05-05T01:00:00",
    "isCurrent": true,
    "assignedTo": "Agent Carter",
    "isV2LegacyCase": true
  },
  "caseOverview": {
    "id": 1234567890,
    "currentFlowchartPosition": "Relief",
    "currentDecision": "56 days relief duty - help to secure accommodation s.189B",
    "houseHoldComposition": "F"
  },
  "placementInformation": [
    {
      "placementType": "Accommodation secured by the Local Authority",
      "fullAddressDetails": {
        "id": 438203,
        "apartment": null,
        "roomNumber": null,
        "houseName": null,
        "houseNumber": "435",
        "street": "Loxford Lane",
        "locality": null,
        "town": "Ilford",
        "county": "",
        "postcode": "SW1 1AA",
        "latitude": null,
        "longitude": null,
        "freetext": null
      },
      "placementDuty": "Section 188",
      "placementDutyFullName": "Section 188 â€“ Interim duty to accommodate in case of apparent priority need",
      "usage": "Temporary Accommodation",
      "dclgClassificationType": "Hostels (including reception centres and emergency units)"
    }
  ],
  "additionalFactors": [
    {
      "legend": "Overview of additional factors",
      "info": [
        {
          "question": "Drug/alcohol use?",
          "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "question": "Care history?",
          "answer": "No"
        },
        {
          "question": "Served in the Armed Forces?",
          "answer": "No"
        },
        {
          "question": "Prison history?",
          "answer": "No"
        },
        {
          "question": "Health Issues?",
          "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "question": "Detail current medication and dosage for all household members",
          "answer": "Mertazerpene x 1 per day."
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "healthAndWellBeing": [
    {
        "legend": "Health and wellbeing",
        "info": [
            {
                "question": "Do you or any of your household members have any self-reported vulnerabilities - including physical or mental health needs? ",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details:",
                "answer": "wheelchair/depression"
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you or any member of your household have any confirmed medical conditions?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details:",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Are you or your family members on any medication?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details:",
                "answer": "anti depressant"
            },
            {
                "question": "Does your current housing situation impact on your medical condition? ",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details:",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you or your family members have any other health care professionals working with you?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details including consultants, health visitors, community psychiatric nurse, occupational therapist etc.",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you use alcohol and/or drugs?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details including how this affects your life",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Does any member of your household require any assistance with addiction (gambling, drugs or alcohol)?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "If so, who and what addiction",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you or any member of your household need support to be able to live independently or to develop independent living skills?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details:",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you or any member of your household ever been in local authority care? ",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "If yes, please provide details: ",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the name of your family GP?",
                "answer": null
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "legend": "Mobility or support issues - Jacqueline Marcus",
        "info": [
            {
                "question": "Does this member of the household have any of the following mobility or support issues?",
                "answer": null
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "legend": "COVID-19 - Jacqueline Marcus",
        "info": [
            {
                "question": "Have you or anyone close to you had any Covid 19 related symptoms within the last 14 days?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "Date symptoms presented or best estimate",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you received your COVID-19 Vaccinations?",
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "question": "Date of first dose",
                "answer": null
            },
            {
                "question": "Date of second dose",
                "answer": null
            }
        ]
    }
]
}
